[
  {
    "question": "What food category does Simon belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Fruitarian diet",
      "b": "Lacto vegetarianism",
      "c": "Vegan diet"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Stuart belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Intermittent fasting",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Cookie diet"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Vala belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Kangatarian",
      "b": "Plant-based diet",
      "c": "Cookie diet"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Tayo belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "The Hacker's Diet",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Inedia"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Bartek belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Atkins diet",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Inedia"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Tim belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "South Beach Diet",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Stillman diet"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Colin belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "South Beach Diet",
      "b": "Inedia",
      "c": "Body for Life"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Thomas belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "The Hacker's Diet",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Inedia"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Sean belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Intermittent fasting",
      "b": "South Beach Diet",
      "c": "Inedia"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Shoshi belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Intermittent fasting",
      "b": "South Beach Diet",
      "c": "Cookie diet"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food category does Andy belong to?",
    "answers": {
      "a": "Kangatarian",
      "b": "Body for Life",
      "c": "Plant-based diet"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  }
]
